<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prayer Planner</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="morningoffer">O my God, in union with the Immaculate Heart of Mary I offer Thee the Precious Blood of Jesus from all the altars throughout the world, joining with it the offering of my every thought, word and action of this day. \n\nO my Jesus, I desire today to gain every indulgence and merit I can and I offer them, together with myself, to Mary Immaculate… that she may best apply them to the interests of Thy most Sacred Heart. \n\nPrecious Blood of Jesus, save us! Immaculate Heart of Mary, pray for us! Sacred Heart of Jesus, have mercy on us!</string>
    <string name="guardianangel">Angel of God, my guardian dear, to whom God\'s love commits me here, ever this day, be at my side, to light and guard, to rule and guide my soul. Amen.</string>
    <string name="gospel_of_day">Daily scripture readings from the Gospel</string>
    <string name="angelous">The Angel of the Lord declared to Mary: And she conceived of the Holy Spirit. \n\nHail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee; blessed art thou among women and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus. Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners, now and at the hour of our death. Amen.\n\nBehold the handmaid of the Lord: Be it done unto me according to Thy word.\n\nHail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee; blessed art thou among women and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus. Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners, now and at the hour of our death. Amen.\n\nAnd the Word was made Flesh: And dwelt among us.\n\nHail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee; blessed art thou among women and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus. Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners, now and at the hour of our death. Amen.\n\nPray for us, O Holy Mother of God, that we may be made worthy of the promises of Christ.\n\nLet us pray: Pour forth, we beseech Thee, O Lord, Thy grace into our hearts; that we, to whom the incarnation of Christ, Thy Son, was made known by the message of an angel, may by His Passion and Cross be brought to the glory of His Resurrection, through the same Christ Our Lord. Amen.</string>
    <string name="divine_mercy_chaplet">Praying the Chaplet of Divine Mercy is a glorious way to enter into the abundant Mercy of God. It is especially good to pray it at three o’clock.</string>
    <string name="memorare">Remember, O most gracious Virgin Mary, that never was it known that anyone who fled to thy protection, implored thy help, or sought thine intercession was left unaided.\n\nInspired by this confidence, I fly unto thee, O Virgin of virgins, my mother; to thee do I come, before thee I stand, sinful and sorrowful. O Mother of the Word Incarnate, despise not my petitions, but in thy mercy hear and answer me. Amen.</string>
    <string name="st_joseph_memorare">Remember, most pure spouse of Mary, ever Virgin, my loving protector, Saint Joseph, that no one ever had recourse to your protection or asked for your aid without obtaining relief.\n\nConfiding therefore, in your goodness, I come before you and humbly implore you. Despise not my petitions, foster-father of the Redeemer, but graciously receive them. Amen.</string>
    <string name="magnificiant">My soul proclaims the greatness of the Lord, and my spirit rejoices in God my Savior, for he has looked with favour on his lowly servant. From this day on all generations will call me blessed: for the Almighty has done great things for me, and holy is his Name. His loving mercy is from age to age for those who fear Him. He has made known the strength of his arm, and has scattered the proud of heart. He has put down the mighty from their thrones, and has exalted those who are lowly. He has filled the hungry with good things, and has sent the rich away empty. He has always helped Israel His servant, mindful of His loving mercy, even as He promised our fathers, to Abraham and his descendants forever. Amen.</string>
    <string name="act_of_faith">Act of Faith\nO my God, I firmly believe that you are one God in three divine Persons, Father, Son and Holy Spirit; I believe that your divine Son became man and died for our sins, and that he shall come to judge the living and the dead. I believe these and all the truths which the holy Catholic Church teaches, because you have revealed them, who can neither deceive nor be deceived.\n\nAct of Hope\nO my God, relying on your almighty power and infinite mercy and promises, I hope to obtain pardon of my sins, the help of your grace, and life everlasting, through the merits of Jesus Christ, my Lord and Redeemer.\n\nAct of Love\nO my God, I love you above all things, with my whole heart and soul, because you are all-good and worthy of all love. I love my neighbor as myself for the love of you. I forgive all who have injured me and ask pardon of all whom I have injured.</string>
    <string name="holy_souls_prayer">Eternal Father, I offer Thee the Most Precious Blood of Thy Divine Son, Jesus, in union with the masses said throughout the world today, for all the holy souls in purgatory, for sinners everywhere, for sinners in the universal church, those in my own home and within my family. Amen.\n\nEternal rest grant unto them, O Lord; And let perpetual light shine upon them. May they rest in peace. Amen</string>
    <string name="holy_rosary">The purpose of the Rosary is to help keep in mind the key events in the history of our salvation. There are twenty mysteries to reflect on in the Rosary, and you can pray these today by selecting one below.</string>
    <string name="st_bridget">Saint Bridget prayed for a long time to know how many blows Our Lord suffered during His terrible Passion. Rewarding her patience, one day He appeared to her and said: I received 5,475 blows upon My Body. If you wish to honour them in some way, recite fifteen Our Fathers and fifteen Hail Marys with the following Prayers, which I Myself shall teach you, for an entire year. When the year is finished, you will have honoured each of My Wounds.</string>
    <string name="deliverence_prayers">Heavenly Father, I praise and thank you for all you have given me. Please cover me with the protective Precious Blood of Your Son Jesus Christ, and increase your Holy Spirit in me with His Gifts of Wisdom, Knowledge, Understanding, Hunger for Prayer, Guidance and Discernment to help me know Your will and surrender to it more completely.\n\nFather, please heal my negative emotions and any wounds in my heart and spirit. Send the Sword of Your Holy Spirit to sever and break all spells, curses, hexes, voodoo, and all negative genetic, intergenerational and addictive material, past present, or to come, known or unknown, against me, my relationships and family, finances, possessions and ministry.\n\nFather, I forgive and ask forgiveness for my sins and failings, and ask that my whole person - body and mind, heart and will, soul and spirit, memory and emotions, attitudes and values lie cleansed, renewed and protected by the Most Precious Blood of Your Son Jesus.\n\nIn the Name, Power, Blood and Authority of Jesus Christ, I bind and break the power and effect in and around me of any and all evil spirits who are trying to harm me in any way, and I command these spirits and their companion spirits in the + Name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit to leave me peacefully and quietly and go immediately and directly to the Eucharistic Presence of Christ in the nearest tabernacle, to be disposed of by Jesus and never again return to harm me.\n\nDear Holy Spirit, please fill up any void in me to overflowing with Your great love. All this, Father, I pray in the name of Jesus Christ, by the guidance of Your Holy Spirit. Immaculate Heart of Mary, Spouse of the Holy Spirit, please pray for and with me. Amen.\n\nPrayer to St Michael\nSt Michael the Archangel, defend us in the day of battle. Be our safeguard against the wickedness and snares of the devil. May God rebuke him, we humbly pray, and do you, O Prince of the heavenly host, by the power of God cast down to hell Satan and all of the wicked spirits who wander through the world seeking the ruin of souls. Amen.\n\nOur Father\nOur Father, who art in Heaven, hallowed be thy name; thy kingdom come; thy will be done on earth as it is in Heaven. Give us this day our daily bread; and forgive us our trespasses as we forgive those who trespass against us; and lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil. Amen.</string>
    <string name="personal_prayers">Spend time in personal prayer with God. Talk to God as a friend, and as a loving Father.\n\nACTS - a Formula for Prayer\nIf you have difficulty thinking of things to say, try following the ACTS formula:\n\nA. Adoration\nStart your prayers with praise. Praise God for who he is. Worship him and acknowledge his greatness.\n\nC. Contrition\nTell God you’re sorry for where you’ve fallen short, where your actions haven’t lived up to God\’s expectations, where haven’t done something you should have. Then, ask God\’s forgiveness and help to do better next time.\n\nT. Thanksgiving\nThank God for His work in your life. Give thanks for all the blessings of this life. As you begin to look for blessings, you’ll be amazed at how many you will find.\n\nS. Supplications\nAsk God for your specific requests for yourself and others. Share what/’s in your heart and where you need God\’s help, guidance, and healing. Pray about the needs others have shared with you and come along beside them in prayer. Submit your heart to God – not my will, God, but yours be done.</string>
    <string name="england_prayer">O blessed Virgin Mary, Mother of God and our most gentle Queen and Mother, look down in mercy upon England thy Dowry and upon us all who greatly hope and trust in thee. By thee it was that Jesus our Saviour and our hope was given unto the world; and He has given thee to us that we might hope still more. Plead for us thy children, whom thou didst receive and accept at the foot of the Cross, O sorrowful Mother. Intercede for our separated brethren, that with us in the one true fold they may be united to the supreme Shepherd, the Vicar of thy Son. Pray for us all, dear Mother, that by faith fruitful in good works we may all deserve to see and praise God, together with thee, in our heavenly home. Amen.</string>
    <string name="holy_spirit_prayer">Come, Holy Spirit, fill the hearts of your faithful. And kindle in them the fire of your love. Send forth your Spirit and they shall be created. And you will renew the face of the earth.\n\nLord, by the light of the Holy Spirit you have taught the hearts of your faithful. In the same Spirit help us to relish what is right and always rejoice in your consolation. We ask this through Jesus Christ our Lord. Amen.</string>
    <string name="night_prayer">Protect us, Lord, as we stay awake; watch over us as we sleep, that awake, we may keep watch with Christ, and asleep, rest in His peace.\n\nLord God, send peaceful sleep to refresh our tired bodies. May your help always renew us and keep us strong in your service. We ask this through Jesus Christ our Lord. Amen.</string>




</resources>